The rules keep changing.
I've been rehearsing every possible outcome.
Once this thought arises, there is no more room for right or wrong.
I am resolved to sever this flood
so that my soul can break free from mediocrity,
from loneliness and distinction.
One more step and you'll fall into madness.
Don't fall down.
I look towards the top.
Chase !
Refined to perfection.
Never retreat, no matter the danger.
I dare to defy the heavens !
Always overcome the obstacles,
ignite the seas with blood,
bloom through trials and tribulations.
Even the sharpest thorns
will be reduced into ashes.
What is there to fear ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
The Ancient Thunder Dragon was born from lightning.
The legends say that back then,
it wielded the Divine Retributions on behalf of the law of the heavens.
If I rely on my own strength,
I'll never escape it.
But if I borrow the power of the Abyss,
I still have a glimmer of hope.
Now or never !
Stop !
The cave I saw before
should be nearby.
If I can enter it,
I can use it to resist the suction force.
Found it !
Cave at the bottom
of the Tide Abyss
I did it !
How could there be
a teleportation formation here !?
With the Stop spell, I could slay this beast.
But since it is at death's door
this is the perfect chance to devour it.
Fortune favors the brave.
Seeking the Dao is risky.
Soul Devourer !
Absorb !
1 year later
I only refined 20% of the Ancient Thunder Dragon
but my Origin Soul has already transformed into a Thunder Dragon.
Trying to destroy my Origin Soul now
would be the same as trying to destroy Divine Retribution lightning.
My spells also contain the might of this heavenly lightning.
With this lightning power,
I could even fight a Late stage Ascendant cultivator.
My Origin Soul can't leave my body anymore !
I suppose this barrier
must be the price for transforming my Origin Soul.
I wonder how Senior Zhou Yi is doing
and where the Mosquito Beast is.
My teleportation failed,
the Earth Escape is blocked.
I can't even use the token to enter the Celestial Cave.
This place
is actually a dead end.
Wh...
What is that lightning
in your eyes !?
Back then, you said you knew the Tide Abyss very well
and knew how to escape from this place.
This place...
Where are we ?
The...
The bottom of the Abyss !
I only ever scouted on the periphery.
I never thought I'd come to the bottom !
I don't know how to get out either !
Useless.
Wait !
I don't know the way out
but I know the All-Seer's secret !
As long as you're willing to release me,
I will tell you !
Speak.
You
must swear on your Dao Heart !
I saw Master devour Sun Yun !
For a long time,
disciples of the Heavenly Fate Sect rarely reached the 2nd step.
There are many speculations about this.
Among them
the most widespread theory is
that the All-Seer refines his own domain
by devouring his 2nd step disciples.
I didn't believe it at the time
until that day.
The technique I cultivate can absorb spiritual energy from beasts.
That day,
while I was devouring a mountain spirit beast,
I unintentionally saw its memories.
That mountain spirit beast had witnessed
the battle between Master and Sun Yun
with its own eyes.
Back then, the two were dueling in the sky.
Initially, Sun Yun could fight Master to a draw.
But at the critical moment,
a strange mark lit up on Sun Yun's forehead
which caused him to lose instantly.
And the next second,
he was devoured alive by Master !
In that moment, I understood
that those terrible rumors
were all true.
A strange mark ?
Was it this one ?
Exactly !
At that time,
was Master wearing a gray robe ?
It was gray !
I did find it a bit strange,
I had never seen Master wear a gray robe before !
Back in the Ancient Demon Inheritance,
I already sensed this slaughter energy was problematic.
Sun Yun must have seen through the All-Seer's scheme before that
which is why he didn't cultivate it to completion.
But he still couldn't escape being devoured...
It looks like
the spells the All-Seer passes on to his disciples
are also the shackles he places on them.
I can't stay on Planet Tian Yun
any longer.
This person is ruthless.
I can't just wait for death here !
Unfortunately, my cultivation is too low.
But...
maybe I can reach Ascendant !
Although my Origin Soul is sealed right now,
by borrowing Ascendant origin energy
I might be able to breakthrough.
Reaching Ascendant
isn't entirely hopeless !
Did he just read my thoughts ?
Celestial Emperor Qing Lin's jade slip recorded the Shadow Escape.
But it can only be used by a Celestial Guard...
It might be my chance to escape.
Although the success rate of refining one is slim,
I have no choice but to try.
You have one chance.
If you can reach Ascendant,
I will grant you a great fortune
to help you reach Illusory Yin and Corporeal Yang.
But the condition is
that you will let me refine you into a Celestial Guard
and serve me for 1000 years.
A Celestial Guard ?
Will I retain my consciousness ?
If you're still alive in 1000 years,
I will give you back your freedom and your consciousness.
I will gamble !
I will gamble on me living 1000 years !
Alright,
I am willing !
Now that he's Ascendant,
he's ready to become a Celestial Guard.
Next,
I must refine his physical body.
Unfortunately,
he only achieved copper-rank strength...
Since his body is too weak,
I'll have to borrow the Heavenly Ghosts' strength.
Note: Wang Lin obtained the Heavenly Ghost from Luo Yun of the Heavenly Ghost Sect when he arrived in the Demon Spirit Land.
Refine !
6 months later
Celestial Guard Du Jian
Illusory Yin
An Illusory Yin puppet !
Celestial Emperor Qing Lin truly had impressive means.
Conceal !
With the Celestial Guard's Shadow Escape,
I have a 60% chance to leave this place.
When the token was taking shape,
I failed to get the last sword.
If my guess is correct,
the token condensed from the purple mist
is the token that fell in the tide back then.
This token is the key to opening the true Celestial Cave.
The All-Seer and the others have coveted it for too long
so I must hide it carefully.
I obtained 7 of the 12 Swords' swords.
With them, I can use the Seven Star Sword Formation.
If I also channel it with Divine Retribution Lightning,
it will become even stronger !
Just these artifacts
are not enough.
Maybe...
Wealth...
Let me have a look
at the secrets you are hiding.
The Heavenly Chop !?
Do you know
the meaning of 'Chopping the net' ?
I don't.
Observe the sentient beings
to obtain the essence of this technique.
The sentient beings...
The words 'Chopping the net'...
What's the connection between them ?
3 years later
Chopping the net...
What does 'Chopping the net' mean ?
I get it !
The heavens are a net.
All sentient beings
are intertwined in a myriad of ways.
We are all bound by the rules of the heavens and the earth.
From birth to death,
we all live in a net.
And the Heavenly Chop
severs this very net of heaven and earth.
It severs
the rules that govern all sentient beings !
Once this sword is used,
it can sever one's destiny
and defy the rules !
This is
the Heavenly Chop !
Heavenly Chop
Sever !
In just a few years,
the suction force has increased a lot.
Could there be something else
at the bottom of the Abyss ?
I painstakingly comprehended the Heavenly Chop
thinking I could finally escape
only for it to be all in vain.
Fate...
Destiny...
Everyone’s happiness is different…
What I seek
is to accompany my parents,
to accompany Wan'er...
Yet the Dao I have chosen
is one of solitude.
Since it has come to this,
I won't overthink it.
I might as well use the time I have
to extract the slaughter energy from my body.
The Life Seals are just a manifestation
of the slaughter energy deeply planted within me.
It's bearable
but not enough !
Suction force,
come at me !
Show yourselves !
1 083 222 strands of slaughter energy,
the exact same number of Life Seals I have.
The suction force isn't strong enough...
Celestial Guard,
Shadow Escape !
6 months later
My million Life Seals
have finally been removed !
Greed !
I ordered you to protect my disciples !
How could they have died like this !?
The compass has been giving frequent warnings lately.
Xi Xue...
What exactly have you encountered ?
Fellow cultivators,
I wish to advance the opening of the Demon Spirit Land
by 10 years.
Does anyone have any objections ?
I agree.
I agree !
Wang Lin,
you dared to forcibly remove the Life Seals.
Since that's the case,
I can't let you live.
Celestial Guards are split into the following ranks: gold, silver, copper, iron. Gold being the strongest and iron being the weakest.
Ask
Qi Condensation
the perilous path filled with countless blades.
Foundation Establishment
Can the mundane world be shattered
Core Formation
Nascent Soul
by a child's steadfast heart ?
If the laws of this world
Soul Formation
Soul Transformation
stand in the way,
I'll defy the universe to tread the heavens
Ascendant
and ask this question to the sky.
My heart's deepest wish
is to not kneel before these mountains and rivers.
Don't accept your doomed fate,
karma can be changed.
Unwilling to let go,
my obsessions propel me forward.
Don't be afraid.
Thunder rumbles as I dare to tread through the reincarnation cycle.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.